# Sara Meadows

sameads9@gmail.com | 314.691.3980 | St. Louis, MO

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/sara-meadows

**GitHub** 

github.com/sarameadows

**Portfolio** 

https://saraameadows.herokuapp.com/

# **Summary**

Full Stack Web Developer with an artistic background, well-known as a creative problem solver, passionate about developing applications with a beautiful interface and an engaging user experience. I enjoy collaborating with others as well as learning about the latest technologies as part of my curious and analytical nature.

#### **Technical Skills**

Frontend: HTML5, CSS, JQuery, Javascript, Bootstrap, AJAX

Backend: MySQL, MongoDB, Express, ReactJS, Node, Handlebars, Webpack, APIs

#### **Education**

Washington University, St. Louis

October 2022

Full Stack Web Development Certificate

Maryville University, St. Louis

December 2021

Bachelor of Fine Arts in Photography, Minor in Studio Art

# **Relevant Work Experience**

Esther & Mila

June 2022 - Present

Creative Production Lead

St. Louis, MO

 Wordpress website management, Product and Lifestyle Photography, Jewelry Designer, Brand development, Inventory management, Sales

Saettele Jewelers October 2021 - June 2022

Sales Associate & Marketing Assistant

St. Louis. MO

Wordpress website management, Product Photography, Sales, Client relations, Social Media

#### Whitebridge Pet Brands

August 2018 - September 2019

Marketing Assistant

St. Louis, MO

 Optimized influencer program for several pet brands, Inventory management, Assisted with projects for Chewy and Amazon

# **Additional Work Experience**

Craft Alliance June 2021 - April 2022

Metal and Glass Faculty St. Louis, MO

Adidas April 2019 - October 2020

Supervisor St. Louis, MO

#### **Awards/Honors**

ALD Honor Society, 2018-2021 / Dean's List, 2017-2021 / Maryville's Innovators of Tomorrow, 2017